articlesproductions.com 2010-11-30

# Article Productions :: article marketing, article directory, content syndication, article marketer, article syndication

ArticleProductions.com respects your privacy, and we want you to feel comfortable using ArticleProductions.com's website and services. Therefore, we present this privacy policy so you can better and fully understand how we collect information about you, what we do with your information, and who, other than ArticleProductions.com, may also receive your information.

 **Customer & Membership Information**  
ArticleProductions.com at the time of registration collects a new member's personal information which includes, but is not limited to, name, address, phone number, email, a user created name and password along with possibly credit card or other financial information.  Once that information is obtained it is added to a secure database that is only used and accessed by ArticleProductions.com's owner in order to provide and maintain the services of the website ArticleProductions.com. All personal information is held in the strictest of confidence.  ArticleProductions.com will not sell, rent, or trade any user's account or personal information. 

**Personal Information**  
ArticleProductions.com does track and keep a record of your IP address for the purpose of cross-checking accounts for security reasons and insuring that a member's experience on the ArticleProductions.com website is enjoyed to it's full potential. Member's IP is recorded upon registration and while taking part in an action or browsing the ArticleProductions.com website.

ArticleProductions.com uses cookies and other proven and recognized safe technologies to provide members with a quality experience and to learn how you use this site's services so that we can continually innovate to improve.

 **E-Mail Privacy**  
ArticleProductions.com does send out emails to all members as notification of website updates and other activities. Users and members agree to receive these emailings as long as they remain a member of ArticleProductions.com. Opting out of receiving these emails can only be done by logging into your account, going to your profile and canceling your membership.

 **Email Newsletter & Email Alert Subscription Forms**  
ArticleProductions.com uses a subscription form system for users and members to request information by subscribing to email newsletters. ArticleProductions.com collects that submitted contact information (name and email address among other data) to provide users and members with the information requested. We do not sell or rent any submitted email addresses to any 3rd parties.

ArticleProductions.com provides a confirm opt-in system for the newsletter that a member chooses to receive. We use the submitted email address to confirm the new subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to the requested newsletter. If your active email address connected with your ArticleProductions.com account needs to be changed, that can be done in your personal account information page.

 **Communications With ArticleProductions.com**  
If or when you send email or other communications to ArticleProductions.com, either through the website or regular mail, we can and may retain those communications in order to process your requests and improve the quality of our services.

 **Third Party Advertising Terms & Conditions**  
ArticleProductions.com uses third party advertising companies to serve our ads on our website. To track the effectiveness of these ads and provide a better user experience, these companies use information about user's visits to our website to serve relevant ads. Information collected and used may include IP address, geographical location, their cookie and historical data previously collected. ArticleProductions.com will not provide any personal information to these advertisers when you interact with them or view a targeted ad, however, by viewing or interacting with an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will assume you meet the targeting criteria used to display that ad or ads.

 **Data Security**  
ArticleProductions.com has put reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control and supervision. This includes management procedures and specialized training for those who work directly with our databases. We take measures to protect against the unauthorized access of personal data, including physical security considerations of the stored data. We restrict access to personal data to only those under the employ of ArticleProductions.com who require knowledge of that information in order to operate and deliver our website's services.

 **Affiliate Partner Information**  
All ArticleProductions.com affiliate information including (but not limited to) address, phone number, email addresses, and tax id numbers is held in strict confidence. This information is collected only for the purpose of generating commission payments, meeting United States federal tax laws and managing our services.

 **Changes To The Privacy Policy**  
If and when there comes a need or cause for this site's Privacy Policy and use of member's personal information to be changed or amended, details of that change will be prominently displayed on the ArticleProductions.com website.  Members and users are encouraged to periodically review ArticleProductions.com's Privacy Policy in order to always be fully aware of any changes that may impact them and how ArticleProductions.com is always working to insure the top level of security and safety.

 **User Option:**  
Any user or member can decline to submit personal information for any of the services offered on this website, in which case ArticleProductions.com will not be able to provide those services to you.

 **Legal Disclaimer:**  
Though ArticleProductions.com makes every effort to preserve member's privacy, we may disclose your Information if we are required to do so by law enforcement, court order, or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with the law or with a legal process  
* Protect and defend our rights, staff and property  
* Protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website  
* Protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public

 **Contacting this Web Site:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices and policies of ArticleProductions.com, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact support
